<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Testimonials on Bing Academy</title><link>https://bingacademy.github.io/testimonials/</link><description>Recent content in Testimonials on Bing Academy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:37:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bingacademy.github.io/testimonials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://bingacademy.github.io/testimonials/aw/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:05:36 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://bingacademy.github.io/testimonials/aw/</guid><description> &amp;ldquo;I would like to report to you that P’s AP physics scored 4! He also got a B for the second semester AP Physics class. Teacher, you really have the invincible power that is out of this universe, transforming P’s score from Incomplete to B.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;跟老师报告一下，P的AP物理考了四分，第二学期物理拿了B。 老师您真的有超级宇宙无敌的神力，把P的成绩从I变成了B。&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bingacademy.github.io/testimonials/gh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:05:36 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://bingacademy.github.io/testimonials/gh/</guid><description> &amp;ldquo;Bill’s AP scores are great. Thank you very much for the encouragement, especially thank teacher Jia for her encouragement and helpful tutoring. We are grateful to choose you as our conselors.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Bill的AP成绩非常棒非常感谢老师们的鼓励，尤其感谢贾老师耐心和辛勤的教导，遇到你们真的是太幸运了。&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bingacademy.github.io/testimonials/jg/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:05:36 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://bingacademy.github.io/testimonials/jg/</guid><description> &amp;ldquo;Thank you, Teacher Jia, my daughter has scored 5 on both AP Economics test. My child admires you very much. Every time she came back from your tutoring, she would excitedly talked about how you helped her to thoroughly understand the concepts. My second child will definitely study economics and SAT with you.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;谢谢贾老师，孩子两门经济学都考了5分。我孩子非常崇拜您，每次从您那补习回来，都满脸兴奋地说，贾老师讲的太好了！我家老二过几年也要跟您学经济学和SAT.&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bingacademy.github.io/testimonials/jx/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:05:36 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://bingacademy.github.io/testimonials/jx/</guid><description> &amp;ldquo;Thank you very much for your patience and encouragement. Your service is awesome, I will recommend your service to all my friends.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;非常感谢法老师和贾老师的耐心帮助和鼓励。你们的服务非常好，我会向所有的朋友推荐你们的服务。&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bingacademy.github.io/testimonials/mk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:05:36 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://bingacademy.github.io/testimonials/mk/</guid><description> &amp;ldquo;My son’s GPA is not good enough to get into USC. Thank you very much for your help. My son really admires you, saying that you are great at college essay editing.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;肯定是贾老师的帮忙，他才能进USC，他的GPA根本就不合格。我儿子非常欣赏老师，一直说老师改文章很厉害。谢谢老师的帮助。&amp;rdquo;</description></item></channel></rss>